谢谢Rado
Thanks, Rado.
现在我们都知道了ListView非常好用
Now that we know the distinct advantages of using a list view,
可以用它在应用中展示天气预报
we can use a list view to display the list of weather forecasts in our app.
那我们应该修改哪个布局文件来做到呢
Now which file in the layout folder should we modify to accomplish this?
我们需要把ListView直接放进Fragment布局
Well, we want to add the list view directly to the fragment.
你打开fragment_main.xml文件的话
If you open up the fragment_main.xml file,
你可以看到布局里有个作为父视图的RelativeLayout
you'll notice that the layout includes a RelativeLayout as a parent view,
也有个作为子视图TextView
as well as a child TextView.
修改这个文件  用ListView代替TextView
Modify this file so that we show a ListView instead of a TextView
并指定其ID为ListViewForecast便于我们之后引用
and assign it an ID ListViewForecast so we can reference it later.
既然这个布局只有一个子视图
Also, since this layout only contains one child's view,
父布局使用FrameLayout
it would be more efficient to actually switch to a FrameLayout
要比RelativeLayout更好
instead of a RelativeLayout.
这些都做完以后  编译运行你的应用
After you make the changes, compile and run your app.
你会觉得黑屏怪怪的  但是没关系
You will be a little bit underwhelmed with the blank screen, but that's okay.
因为我们还没有给ListView填充数据
That's because we haven't populated the list view with data yet,
这会在下一步实现
and that will come in a later step.
完成了记得来检查一下
Check the box when you're done.